ABOLARIN MARY OLUWAPELUMI

Sagamu, Ogun State | maryabolarin@gmail.com | 0810 8948 282

PROFILE

Reliable Employee with energetic and resourceful customer service professional with over Quality Assurance Specialist with more than 3+ years of quality assurance experience, including testing, implementation, and execution. Excellent at quickly identifying high-level test strategies and problems. Collaborative but decisive personal style and effective communication and problem solving. Ability to cultivate key client relationships for multiple campaigns in diverse industries. Expertise in client services, account management and relationship-building.

WORK HISTORY

Green Apple Agro Allied Limited

May 2018 - Present

Position: Quality Assurance Inspector (Store / Raw Materials)

- Online inspection of defects on production
- Analyzing and controlling of defects in store
- Record keeping of Store condition
- Maintain all reports and records
- Inspection of Mixing Dosages of Materials used on Production floor.
- Monitoring/Inspection of Incoming Raw materials (PP Resin, PET)
- Monitor all parameter and keeping them under limits.
- Lead and encourage team to maintain Clean and hygienic working conditions in the store.

Goodness and Mercy Computer Institute

April 2017 – May 2018

Position: Clerk

- Received 97% satisfaction rating from customers after completed phone or video calls.
- Kept records of customer interactions, processed customer accounts and filed documents.
- Collaborated with the team to quickly resolve customer complaints with the appropriate action.
- Typesetting and Documents printing

Future Glory Private School

September 2013 - July 2014

Position: Class Teacher

- Making Weekly class lesson notes
- Ensuring the safety of my pupils and other students
- Monitor my pupils progress and their potentials
- Managing and keeping orderliness in the class.
- Engaging My pupils in various vocational activities.

EDUCATION

Kwara State Polytechnic, Ilorin

2014 - 2016

National Diploma In Purchasing and Supply

CERTIFICATION/TRAINING

2018

ACHIEVEMENTS AND KEY TRAININGS:

- Minimized waste of machine consumables, raw materials, finished and semi finished product waste from Quality Assurance point of view.
- Minimized unplanned downtime in production line by providing strong technical support.
- Overseeing production processes for quality production.
- Ensure clean and safe environments in the company
- Ensured all workers are on Personal Protective Equipment's (PPEs) for safety purpose.
- Keep all records of incoming raw materials and outgoing products.

SKILLS AND INTERESTS

- Marketing
- Excellent communication skills
- Computer Literate (MS: Word and Excel)
- **■** Good Problem Solving Skills
- Store Management
- Strength: Resourceful, Loyal and Trustworthy, Commercially Aware and Disciplined
- Interest: Education, Employability, and Research.

REFEREES

Available on request